<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Inbox Pager</string>
    <string name="author">Copyright &#169; 2016 &#8211; 2020  ITPROJECTS</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">DISCLAIMER:</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">The authors of this software are not liable for ANY damages that this software may cause - accidental or otherwise, under ANY and EVERY law or regulation, and in ANY and EVERY country or territory of the world.</string>
    <string name="dialog_license">License Information</string>
    <string name="license">Application License: General Public License 3</string>
    <string name="license_long" translatable="false">This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.\n\n
        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details.\n\n
        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program. If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/.
    </string>
    <string name="license_media_files" translatable="false">Application Icon:\nCC-BY-SA, Creative Commons Attribution Share Alike 4.0 International Public License</string>
    <string name="license_font" translatable="false">Dottz Font:\nSIL-OFL 1.1 License, ITPROJECTS</string>
    <string name="license_long_font" translatable="false">Copyright (&#169;) 2016 &#8211; 2020 ITPROJECTS\n\nSIL OPEN FONT LICENSE\n\nVersion 1.1 - 26 February 2007\nPREAMBLE\n\nThe goals of the Open Font License (OFL) are to stimulate worldwide development of collaborative font projects,
        to support the font creation efforts of academic and linguistic communities, and to provide a free and open framework in which fonts may be shared and improved in partnership with others.\n\n
        The OFL allows the licensed fonts to be used, studied, modified and redistributed freely as long as they are not sold by themselves. The fonts, including any derivative works, can be bundled, embedded,
        redistributed and/or sold with any software provided that any reserved names are not used by derivative works. The fonts and derivatives, however, cannot be released under any other type of license.
        The requirement for fonts to remain under this license does not apply to any document created using the fonts or their derivatives.\n\n
        DEFINITIONS\n\n
        "Font Software" refers to the set of files released by the Copyright Holder(s) under this license and clearly marked as such. This may include source files, build scripts and documentation.\n\n"Reserved Font Name" refers to any names specified as such after the copyright statement(s).\n\n
        "Original Version" refers to the collection of Font Software components as distributed by the Copyright Holder(s).\n\n"Modified Version" refers to any derivative made by adding to, deleting, or substituting — in part or in whole — any of the components of the
        Original Version, by changing formats or by porting the Font Software to a new environment.\n\n"Author" refers to any designer, engineer, programmer, technical writer or other person who contributed to the Font Software.\n\nPERMISSION and CONDITIONS\n\n
        Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of the Font Software, to use, study, copy, merge, embed, modify, redistribute, and sell modified and unmodified copies of the Font Software, subject to the following conditions:\n\n
        1) Neither the Font Software nor any of its individual components, in Original or Modified Versions, may be sold by itself.\n\n
        2) Original or Modified Versions of the Font Software may be bundled, redistributed and/or sold with any software, provided that each copy contains the above copyright notice and this license. These can be included either as stand-alone text files, human-readable headers or in the appropriate
        machine-readable metadata fields within text or binary files as long as those fields can be easily viewed by the user.\n\n
        3) No Modified Version of the Font Software may use the Reserved Font Name(s) unless explicit written permission is granted by the corresponding Copyright Holder. This restriction only applies to the primary font name as presented to the users.\n\n
        4) The name(s) of the Copyright Holder(s) or the Author(s) of the Font Software shall not be used to promote, endorse or advertise any Modified Version, except to acknowledge the contribution(s) of the Copyright Holder(s) and the Author(s) or with their explicit written permission.\n\n
        5) The Font Software, modified or unmodified, in part or in whole, must be distributed entirely under this license, and must not be distributed under any other license. The requirement for fonts to remain under this license does not apply to any document created using the Font Software.\n\n
        TERMINATION\n\nThis license becomes null and void if any of the above conditions are not met.\n
        DISCLAIMER\n\n
        THE FONT SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT OF COPYRIGHT, PATENT, TRADEMARK, OR OTHER RIGHT.
        IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, INCLUDING ANY GENERAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
        OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE FONT SOFTWARE OR FROM OTHER DEALINGS IN THE FONT SOFTWARE.</string>
    <string name="license_open_keychain">OpenKeychain (Java) Apache License, Version 2.0.</string>
    <string name="license_long_open_keychain" translatable="false">Copyright (&#169;) Copyright (C) 2016 &#8211; 2020  ITPROJECTS\nCopyright (&#169;) 2013 &#8211; 2015 Dominik Schürmann dominik@dominikschuermann.de\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
        you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\n
        Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an
        "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
        See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.\n
    </string>
    <string name="license_apache_foundation" translatable="false">Apache Software Foundation Classes Apache License, Version 2.0.</string>
    <string name="license_long_apache_foundation" translatable="false">Copyright (&#169;) 2004 The Apache Software Foundation\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
        you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\n
        Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an
        "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
        See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.\n
    </string>
    <string name="license_sql_cipher_java">SQLCipher (Java) Apache License, Version 2.0.</string>
    <string name="license_long_sql_cipher_java" translatable="false">Copyright (&#169;) 2006 The Android Open Source Project\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
        you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\n
        Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an
        "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
        See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.\n
    </string>
    <string name="license_sql_cipher_other">SQLCipher (Other Components)</string>
    <string name="license_long_sql_cipher_other" translatable="false">Copyright (&#169;) 2010 Zetetic LLC All rights reserved.\n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n\n
        * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n
        * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n
        * Neither the name of the ZETETIC LLC nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.\n\n
        THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY ZETETIC LLC \'\'AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
        DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL ZETETIC LLC BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
        LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE,
        EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    </string>
    <string name="license_gnu_cryoto" translatable="false">Gnu Crypto, General Public License 2</string>
    <string name="license_long_gnu_cryoto" translatable="false">Copyright (C) 2001, 2002, 2003 Free Software Foundation, Inc.\n\nThis file is part of GNU Crypto.\n\n GNU Crypto is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the
        GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2, or (at your option) any later version.\n\nGNU Crypto is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty
        of\nMERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License for more details.\n\nYou should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; see the file COPYING.  If not, write to the\n\n
        Free Software Foundation Inc.,\n   59 Temple Place - Suite 330,\n   Boston, MA 02111-1307\n   USA\n\nLinking this library statically or dynamically with other modules is\nmaking a combined work based on this library.  Thus, the terms and\nconditions of
        the GNU General Public License cover the whole\ncombination.\n\nAs a special exception, the copyright holders of this library give you permission to link this library with independent modules to produce an executable, regardless of the license terms of
        these independent modules, and to copy and distribute the resulting executable under terms of your choice, provided that you also meet, for each linked independent module, the terms and conditions of the license of that module.  An independent module is
        a module which is not derived from or based on this library.  If you modify this library, you may extend this exception to your version of the library, but you are not obligated to do so.  If you do not wish to do so, delete this exception statement from your version.</string>
    <string name="cc_by_sa" translatable="false">Stack Overflow Material</string>
    <string name="cc_by_sa_link" translatable="false">creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0\n\ncreativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/legalcode</string>
    <string name="cc_by_sa_long" translatable="false">\nModified X.509\nCertificate identification\n\nSuggested by Julio López Torres\ngithub.com/juliolopeztorres\n\nFrom an answer by HTLee:\nstackoverflow.com/questions/32573317/how-to-determine-length-of-x509-public-key\n\n</string>

    <!-- Progress Dialog Spinner -->
    <string name="progress_title">Refreshing</string>
    <string name="progress_refreshing">Looking for changes…</string>
    <string name="progress_nothing">No (new) messages.</string>
    <string name="progress_not_found">No such message.</string>
    <string name="progress_fetch_msg">Fetching message…</string>
    <string name="progress_fetch_attachment">Fetching attachment…</string>
    <string name="progress_deleting_msg">Deleting message…</string>
    <string name="progress_deleting">Deleting…</string>
    <string name="progress_deleted_msgs">messages deleted.</string>
    <string name="progress_deleted_msg">Message deleted.</string>
    <string name="progress_downloading">Downloading…</string>
    <string name="progress_download_complete">Download complete.</string>
    <string name="progress_connecting">Connecting to</string>
    <string name="progress_connected">Connected.</string>
    <string name="progress_authenticated">Authenticated.</string>

    <!-- Account Statistics Dialog -->
    <string name="stats_title">Account Situation</string>
    <string name="stats_messages">messages</string>
    <string name="stats_unseen">unseen</string>

    <!-- Exception Dialog -->
    <string name="ex_title">Problem</string>
    <string name="ex_do_io">Unable to do network IO operations.</string>
    <string name="ex_field">Exception:</string>
    <string name="ex_ran_out_of_ram">Not enough RAM. Free more virtual memory.</string>
    <string name="ex_no_remote_address">Mail server not found.</string>
    <string name="ex_no_internet">No internet! Check your connection.</string>

    <!-- Attachments List Dialog -->
    <string name="attch_title">Download To</string>
    <string name="attch_bytes">B</string>
    <string name="attch_kilobytes">KB</string>
    <string name="attch_megabytes">MB</string>
    <string name="attch_added_attachment">Added:</string>

    <!-- Folder Picker Dialog -->
    <string name="folder_title">FOLDER</string>
    <string name="file_title">FILES</string>
    <string name="picker_pick">PICK</string>

    <!-- Error Dialogs -->
    <string name="err_title_write_perms">Writing Prohibited</string>
    <string name="err_msg_write_perms">You do not have the folder permission to save your file in your chosen folder.</string>
    <string name="err_title_no_space">No space</string>
    <string name="err_msg_no_space">You do not seem to have enough space on your device to save this file.</string>
    <string name="err_title_file_is_duplicate">File is already attached.</string>
    <string name="err_title_android_permission">Android Permissions</string>
    <string name="err_wrong_user_or_pass">Wrong user name or password</string>
    <string name="err_read_file">You do not have the permission to read this file.</string>
    <string name="err_size_attachments_title">Attachments Problem</string>
    <string name="err_size_attachments">Your attachments are larger than the outgoing server will allow. Remove some attachments.</string>
    <string name="err_size_attachments_continue">Ignore and Continue</string>
    <string name="err_no_rcpt">No recipient!</string>
    <string name="err_too_many_rcpt">Too many recipients. Maximum is 100.</string>
    <string name="err_msg_too_heavy">Try removing attachments and/or sending text in multiple messages.</string>
    <string name="err_no_8_bit_mime">8-BIT server transfer support missing. Attachment transfer errors are possible.</string>
    <string name="err_no_authentication">Server does not seem to support the authentication types used by this application.</string>
    <string name="err_no_ehlo">Server does not support the EHLO extensions listing command.</string>
    <string name="err_no_capability">Server does not support the CAPABILITY listing command.</string>
    <string name="err_no_capa">Server does not support the CAPA extensions listing command.</string>
    <string name="err_no_extension">Server does not support either AUTH/SASL or UIDL extension.</string>
    <string name="err_pop_immediate">Server deletes emails after reading.</string>
    <string name="err_pop_expiration">Server deletes emails after %s days.</string>
    <string name="err_server_not_configured">Outgoing server has not been configured correctly.</string>
    <string name="err_not_saved">Could not complete save action.</string>
    <string name="err_imap_attachment_saving">Offline attachment file saving failed. Download attachment online and delete full message from database.</string>
    <string name="err_action_failed">Action failed (see log).</string>
    <string name="err_refresh">Errors in</string>
    <string name="err_pick_signing_key">Pick a signing key!</string>
    <string name="err_pick_rcpt_keys">Pick recipient keys!</string>
    <string name="err_missing_crypto_mime">Missing message cryptographic data!</string>

    <!-- InboxPager activity -->
    <string name="activity_pw">PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="activity_pager_title">Pager</string>
    <string name="menu_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_add_account">Add Account</string>
    <string name="no_accounts">Add Message Accounts</string>
    <string name="select_account">Select Inbox</string>
    <string name="btn_log_clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open Inbox List</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close Inbox List</string>
    <string name="helper_title">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="helper_msg">Have an enjoyable messaging, and remember to setup a data protection password, in the settings menu, or your accounts may get easily compromised.</string>
    <string name="btn_pw">SET PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="btn_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="btn_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="btn_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="menu_all_seen">Mark All Read</string>
    <string name="menu_log">Errors / Exceptions</string>
    <string name="menu_status">Inbox Status</string>
    <string name="menu_port_consideration_title">Confirm Port</string>
    <string name="menu_port_consideration_dialog">Are you sure this is the correct port?</string>
    <string name="menu_delete_account_dialog_title">Confirm Deletion</string>
    <string name="menu_delete_account_dialog">Are you sure you want to delete this account?</string>
    <string name="menu_switch_pop_imap_title">Confirm Switch</string>
    <string name="menu_switch_pop_imap_dialog">Switching between IMAP and POP requires all local messages to be deleted and then added from the server. Continue?</string>
    <string name="ssl_auth_popup_title">Last Connection</string>
    <string name="ssl_auth_popup_bad_connection">You may be experiencing NO SECURITY AT ALL! Remote server had bad or missing SSL/TLS certificates, or the host name cannot be verified.</string>
    <string name="no_messages">Empty Inbox</string>

    <!-- InboxPreferences activity -->
    <string name="activity_add_account_title">Add Account</string>
    <string name="activity_edit_account_title">Edit This Account</string>
    <string name="edit_account_email">Account Name</string>
    <string name="edit_account_email_hint">your.account@example.com</string>
    <string name="edit_account_username">Username</string>
    <string name="edit_account_pass">Password</string>
    <string name="edit_account_incoming_server_hint_pop" translatable="false">pop.example.com</string>
    <string name="edit_account_incoming_server_port_hint_pop" translatable="false">995</string>
    <string name="edit_account_incoming_server_hint_imap" translatable="false">imap.example.com</string>
    <string name="edit_account_incoming_server_port_hint_imap" translatable="false">993</string>
    <string name="edit_account_imap_or_pop_switchOn" translatable="false">IMAP  pop</string>
    <string name="edit_account_imap_or_pop_switchOff" translatable="false">POP  imap</string>
    <string name="edit_account_imap_or_pop_on" translatable="false">IMAP</string>
    <string name="edit_account_imap_or_pop_off" translatable="false">POP</string>
    <string name="edit_account_smtp" translatable="false">SMTP</string>
    <string name="edit_account_smtp_server_hint" translatable="false">smtp.example.com</string>
    <string name="edit_account_smtp_server_port_hint" translatable="false">465</string>
    <string name="edit_account_auto_check">Allow in all-accounts-refresh</string>
    <string name="edit_account_always_ask_pass">Ask for password every time</string>
    <string name="edit_account_auto_save_full_msgs">Keep full messages in database</string>
    <string name="edit_account_check_save_first">Save account before checking!</string>
    <string name="edit_account_net_checks">On-line tests</string>
    <string name="edit_account_nc_check">Auto Test (Long)</string>
    <string name="edit_account_check_incoming">Try Incoming</string>
    <string name="edit_account_check_smtp">Try Outgoing</string>
    <string name="edit_account_checking">Checking…</string>
    <string name="edit_account_check_login_types">Authentication:</string>
    <string name="edit_account_check_other">Other:</string>
    <string name="edit_account_check_fail">Failed to communicate with server.</string>
    <string name="edit_account_bad_params">Bad parameters</string>
    <string name="edit_account_bad_email">, email</string>
    <string name="edit_account_bad_server">, server</string>
    <string name="edit_account_bad_port">, port</string>
    <string name="edit_account_no_saving">Account needs a name!</string>
    <string name="edit_account_save">SAVE</string>
    <string name="edit_account_saving">Saving…</string>
    <string name="edit_account_not_saved">NOT Saved!</string>
    <string name="edit_account_delete">DELETE</string>
    <string name="edit_account_test_results">Test Results</string>
    <string name="edit_account_pop1" translatable="false">POP3:110</string>
    <string name="edit_account_pop2" translatable="false">POP3S:995</string>
    <string name="edit_account_imap1" translatable="false">IMAP:143</string>
    <string name="edit_account_imap2" translatable="false">IMAPS:993</string>
    <string name="edit_account_smtp1" translatable="false">SMTP:25</string>
    <string name="edit_account_smtp2" translatable="false">SMTPS:465</string>
    <string name="edit_account_smtp3" translatable="false">SMTP:587</string>

    <!-- InboxMessage activity -->
    <string name="menu_download_msg">Download ➠ Database</string>
    <string name="menu_save_message">Save ➠ Device</string>
    <string name="menu_delete_from_server">Delete From Server</string>
    <string name="menu_delete_full_message">Delete Full Message (DB)</string>
    <string name="menu_delete_full_messages">Delete Full Messages</string>
    <string name="menu_delete_messages_keep_settings">Delete Messages, Keep Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_see_full_message">View Full Message</string>
    <string name="menu_see_full_message_title">Full Message</string>
    <string name="message_reply">REPLY</string>
    <string name="message_action_done">Done</string>
    <string name="message_dialog">Received FROM</string>
    <string name="message_from">FROM</string>
    <string name="message_to">TO</string>
    <string name="message_cc">CC</string>
    <string name="message_bcc">BCC</string>
    <string name="message_subject">SUBJECT</string>
    <string name="message_date">DATE</string>
    <string name="message_contents">MESSAGE</string>
    <string name="message_contents_loop_plain">PLAIN</string>
    <string name="message_contents_loop_html">HTML</string>
    <string name="message_date_original">"Original message date:\n\n"</string>
    <string name="message_no_full_message">Full message deleted from database.</string>
    <string name="message_del_messages">Messages deleted from database.</string>

    <!-- InboxSend activity -->
    <string name="send_send">SEND</string>
    <string name="send_sent">Sent.</string>
    <string name="send_spin">Sending…</string>
    <string name="send_addresses_hint" translatable="false">A@foo.com, B@foo.net,</string>
    <string name="send_attachments">Attachments</string>
    <string name="send_wait">Wait a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="send_headers_sent">Headers sent. Sending Contents…</string>
    <string name="send_upload_attachment">Uploading attachment:</string>
    <string name="send_missing_rcpt_to">Missing primary recipient.</string>
    <string name="send_cleartext_subject">Cleartext Subject</string>
    <string name="send_cleartext_content">The subject of the message WILL NOT be encrypted. Would you like to remove the subject of the message for more privacy?</string>
    <string name="send_cleartext_delete">Remove</string>
    <string name="send_cleartext_keep">Keep</string>
    <string name="send_encrypt">Encrypt</string>
    <string name="send_unlock_first">Press UNLOCK button.</string>
    <string name="send_show_previous">Show Previous Message</string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="sett_auto_check_title">Refresh All Inboxes</string>
    <string name="sett_auto_check_summary">Default setting. ALL participating message accounts will be checked, when the home screen refresh button if clicked.</string>
    <string name="sett_beeps_download_title">Beep on new messages</string>
    <string name="sett_beeps_download_summary">Device will make a beeping sound, when new messages arrive.</string>
    <string name="sett_vibrates_download_title">Vibration on new messages</string>
    <string name="sett_vibrates_download_summary">Device will vibrate, when new messages arrive.</string>
    <string name="sett_msg_font_size_title">Font SIZE</string>
    <string name="sett_msg_font_size_summary">Font size for the fields, when viewing a message.</string>
    <string name="sett_enable_pw_title">Password Protection</string>
    <string name="sett_enable_pw_summary_off">Password Status: DISABLED.</string>
    <string name="sett_enable_pw_summary_on">Password Status: ENABLED.</string>
    <string name="sett_change_pw_title">Password</string>
    <string name="sett_change_pw_new">NEW PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="sett_change_pw_retype">REPEAT NEW PASS</string>
    <string name="sett_change_pw_text">>= 12 symbols</string>
    <string name="sett_change_pw_q">Remove or Change Password?</string>
    <string name="sett_change_pw_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="sett_change_pw_change">Change</string>
    <string name="sett_change_pw_vis" translatable="false">👁</string>
    <string name="sett_crypto_type_title">Cryptogram Encryption Algorithm</string>
    <string name="sett_crypto_type_summary">AES/Twofish. This does not encrypt attachments.</string>
    <string name="sett_crypto_mode_title">Cryptogram Encryption Mode</string>
    <string name="sett_crypto_mode_summary">CBC/CTR/ECB/ICM/OFB. This does not encrypt attachments.</string>
    <string name="sett_crypto_padding_title">Cryptogram Text Padding</string>
    <string name="sett_crypto_padding_summary">PKCS/TBC. This does not encrypt attachments.</string>

    <!-- GPG -->
    <string name="open_pgp_dialog_title">Cryptography</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_reset">RESET</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_ready">READY</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_start" translatable="false">GPG</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_press_start">Press GPG button.</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_none_found">OpenKeychain not found! No encryption/decryption!!</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_list_items_encrypt">ENCRYPT MESSAGE</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_list_items_sign_encrypt">SIGN AND ENCRYPT MESSAGE</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_list_items_detach_sign">SIGN CLEAR TEXT MESSAGE</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_list_items_decrypt_and_verify">DECRYPT AND VERIFY</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_signing_key_check">&#10003; Signing key</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_signing_key_cross">&#10060; Signing key</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_rcpt_key_check">&#10003; Recipient keys</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_rcpt_key_cross">&#10060; Recipient keys</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_recipients">RECIPIENTS</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_message">CLEAR MESSAGE</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_message_encrypted_block">ENCRYPTED MESSAGE</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_message_signature">SIGNATURE</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_bad_signature">No signatures, bad signature, or a transmission error.</string>
    <string name="open_pgp_encrypt_to_self">Also encrypt to signing key</string>
    <string name="err_no_full_msg">Full message not found in database. Download from server first.</string>
    <string name="message_contents_loop_no">NO TEXT</string>

    <!-- Other Crypto -->
    <string name="empty_string" translatable="false"/>
    <string name="crypto_title">Encrypted Text</string>
    <string name="crypto_key_32_symbols">=&lt; 32 symbols</string>
    <string name="crypto_plain_warning">Encrypt or Decrypt text of message, with key below.</string>
    <string name="crypto_encrypt">&#128274; Encrypt</string>
    <string name="crypto_decrypt">&#128275; Decrypt</string>
    <string name="crypto_no_text">Missing message text.</string>
    <string name="crypto_invalid_key">Invalid KEY OR LENGTH.</string>
    <string name="crypto_success">SUCCESS!</string>
    <string name="crypto_failure">FAILURE!</string>
    <string name="crypto_failed_encryption">Failed encryption for %s/%s/%s.</string>
    <string name="crypto_failed_decryption">Failed decryption for %s/%s/%s.</string>
    <string name="crypto_failed_unpadding">Failed removal of padding %s.</string>
    <string name="crypto_bad_message">Message does not have BASE64.</string>
    <string name="crypto_unsupported">UNSUPPORTED</string>

    <string name="crypto_pgp" translatable="false">PGP</string>
    <string name="crypto_txt" translatable="false">CRYPTOGRAM</string>

    <!-- Values must match those in crypto class -->
    <string-array name="crypto_ciphers">
        <item translatable="false">AES</item>
        <item translatable="false">Twofish</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Values must match those in crypto class -->
    <string-array name="crypto_cipher_modes">
        <item translatable="false">CBC</item>
        <item translatable="false">CTR</item>
        <item translatable="false">ECB</item>
        <item translatable="false">ICM</item>
        <item translatable="false">OFB</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Values must match those in crypto class -->
    <string-array name="crypto_cipher_paddings">
        <item translatable="false">PKCS7</item>
        <item translatable="false">TBC</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
